Okay, can we see that? Okay, everyone. Yeah. Yeah, I can see. Yeah, so
hopefully everyone
knows kind of. So welcome to our call on webcam essentials. So yeah, it's a
great
call for any newbies just to get some tips and learn the basics. If anybody has
got anything
that we don't cover in this call, that is, you know, a tip from you because we
can all
learn from each other, then please don't hesitate to put it in the chat box or
just let us know
at the end. We'd love to hear your tips as well. Okay, so what shall we cover
in this
call? So we'll have a look at your profile. So enabling your profile. What's
important
with that? Treating this as a business because of course it's a business just
like any other.
The different styles of webcam and some of the different ways that you can show
up on
getting more clients. Sami's expert advice, the lovely Sami. Looking after you,
so looking
at your well-being and a few little extra things to note and of course you can
ask any questions
or give your own tips or advice at the end. Okay, Georgia, do you want to go?
Yeah, of
course. So we've spoke about the importance of the profile quite often but we
're just
going to go over it again because there's some new people here and even if you
're not
new it's still very important to always go back through and update your profile
as you
go through the journey on webcam because one, you'll be changing what you want
to do and
what you like and your pictures and whatnot and also it's just good to update
it even
if you're not really changing much, you just add in more. So the first thing
you can look
at is your bio. So in your bio we recommend really just kitting it out as much
as possible
so you can start off by having a little tagline at the top but then underneath
is where most
of the text is going to be and in there you can write about what you enjoy on
cam but
also what you enjoy in your day to day life but this can be made up as well, it
doesn't
have to actually be personal to you, just personal to your webcam persona and
if you
do this it just makes you look a little bit more like a real human that they
can connect
with rather than just like a porn star online or whatever because you know that
's not what
we are so we want to show them that we are real humans that they can connect
with and
in your bio you can also add different tabs to speak about different parts of
your personality
and what you like on cam and we actually have quite a few documents that can
talk you through
exactly what to do and what to write on here so we can always send you them
afterwards
if you need any more help but yes that's a little bit about the bio. It's also
good as
well to just take a look at what other girls are writing on the website not to
copy them
but just maybe get some inspiration of what to write and what to say and you
can also
ask your mentors and ask me an L as well if you need any more advice on that
one and
okay so moving on so another thing that you can add on your profile is pictures
so your
free profile pictures are your main ones so on there you want to pick your best
ones
and pick your very best one for your main profile picture. You want to pick a
photo as
well where you're taking up most of the screen because when you're showing up
online you
just show up as a very small photo mixed in with all of the photos of the other
girls
so you want it to be super eye-catching so you don't want to be a small dot on
that
photo you want to be taken up the whole screen so they can see you and you can
also have
a free and private gallery so the free gallery they obviously see these
pictures for free
so don't put anything to revealing in there and in your private gallery they
have to pay
to see these so this is where you'd put your more seductive pictures if you
have any like
that and you can also create albums for certain clients so let's say for
example you have
a foot fetish client and he wants just a whole album of your feet then you can
make
a album of pictures of your feet and give them a code and then they have to put
the
code in to be able to access it and then they have to pay to access it too so
yeah
that's another thing you can do for your individual clients so drawing in your
ideal
client so with on your profile and when you write about what you like on cam
and what
you enjoy and what not you're basically writing this for your ideal client so
have a think
about what type of words you're using and what teams you're using and how you
're describing
yourself and stuff like that because setting clients are going to be drawn to
setting profiles
and so yeah just think about what your who your ideal client is and then think
about
what you might write which will draw them in okay so ratings and given feedback
this
one I feel like it's actually quite important because the more ratings you have
on the website
I feel like your profile looks a little bit more inviting for clients because
you look
more established and obviously you look like you know that you're a real
profile you're
not just like a fake one or any well you can't really have fake ones but you
know some profiles
on there when the brand new and they haven't got many ratings it can be hard to
try and
build up clients but when you've got a lot of ratings it seems a little bit
easier and
a good way to get ratings is actually by giving ratings to your clients so
everyone that you
can with if it's over a couple of minutes and if the session if the session is
just a few
seconds and you won't get the option to but if it's been a couple of minutes in
the session
at least you'll get the option to give your clients feedback and to do this you
just click
on the emails and bookings tab on your profile and if you forget any of this
what we said
by the way just always ask your mentor you how to do it and we'll just tell you
straight
away so you click on emails and bookings and then it'll pop up to say you have
some outstanding
feedback to leave or something like that it'll say along those lines so you can
just click
on okay and then it'll come up with a list of all your clients and a little box
where
you can leave feedback for your clients so it's positive neutral and negative I
think
it is and then a little you can leave a little bit of text so obviously I
always want to
leave positive ones well unless it was a really bad session of course but even
then I probably
would just report them to add a work rather than leave them a negative feedback
because
I don't you wouldn't want to get one back and so yes you can leave them
positive feedback
and then write a little bit in there about them or about the session and if you
don't
remember who they was or how the session went you can just say something
generic like had
such a great time with you can't wait to come with you again or something like
that but
what would be better is if you did remember maybe something that was said in
the session
or something like that you know can't wait to dom you again or can't wait for
you to tell
me how much of a naughty little girl I am or something like that I don't know
whatever
it is that was being said in the session my mum's dad's office is I'm like I
hope they
can't hear me oh well they know what to do and so yes leaving feedback for your
clients
is important because then hopefully they will see it and then leave it for you
some
people ask their clients to leave them feedback and some don't I think it just
depends on
what type of webcam persona you have and you know what relationship you have of
your clients
some clients I ask and some of them I wouldn't so just you know maybe you'll
think oh yeah
this this client he seems like he's a nice guy that would want to do something
to make
me feel good or something to make me happy so I'll ask him to leave me a
feedback and
you know tell him that you really appreciate it and stuff like that and so yeah
you can
always ask your clients as well if you feel like they're the type of client
that would
respond well to that okay so direct I am SMS and phone calls so as well as
webcam you can
make money on direct I am which is and basically like webcam but without the
calm so it's just
a live chat kind of like MNS no what was it MNS is always calls no what was a
call back
in the day I can't remember now there was one back in the day that we all used
to use
and it was just this basically like that and SMN that's it yeah SMN messenger
and thank
you Hannah yeah so it's just basically a live chat without the calm and so this
is good
to do if you know you're around people that you can't come around like maybe
you're sat
and you know your parents or whoever else is around you and you don't want to
put your
cam on but you can just sat on your phone or your laptop and you can just be
chatting
on a way no one's ever going to know or maybe on the train or out and about or
maybe you
don't want to do your hair and makeup and you just feel like you don't want
anyone to
see you that day you can pop your direct I am on and I feel like over the past
couple
of months quite a lot of our girls have been doing this and we see really good
feedback
with this you know them saying like oh I just threw it on you know I would know
expectation
and they made like 60 credits or you know 100 credits or whatever and it feels
like a
really simple and easy to do it and they don't even get to see you so it's a
lot less I feel
like it's less effort for you so yeah that's always one to consider if you're
not on come
and and we can show you how to flick this on and off as well so if you're
interested
just ask us and we'll tell you exactly how to do it and so SMS and phone calls
as well
as another way you could make money on there so this is really good for
connecting with
your regular clients outside of webcam so if you if you've got the option to do
SMS and
phone calls I would definitely recommend trying it because you can always text
your clients
and tell them when you're going to be online or just continue the conversation
outside
of come and you make money every single time they send a text and it doesn't
cost you anything
and the phone calls as well the same thing they have to pay like I said I'm on
the credits
to be able to phone you and and then yeah it's just another way to connect with
your clients
and just keep them keep them hooked basically and so yeah we can help you
settle all this
up if you're interested as well and finally your profile changes with you so as
I said
earlier and you can always change your profile whenever you like I update mine
regularly
and I think it's important to do that and also you can literally just change it
completely
so you might start off with your profile a certain way thinking that's how you
would
like to do calm but then after a while you might think actually I want to take
it down
a different route and you can change it up completely that's no problem you can
change
basically everything on there you name your pictures bio everything so you can
make it
like a brand new profile if you wanted to so just bear that in mind just to
always change
it up and update it and just keep it current of how how you feel and how you
want to present
yourself on come hey it's cute seeing the pictures coming out because I haven't
seen
what pictures you've got on this day yeah these are from our recent shoes I
love these
pictures so cute okay so this is your business so it's important to invest your
time and
energy into this job and to treat it like a real business because it is of
course and
if you apply yourself fully the possibilities are endless and knowledge is
power so of course
and then we say all the time but we've got so much training on the website and
even if
you're just like doing your makeup getting ready for cam or whatever you know
you can
have it playing in the background and you know some of our calls we've got
different people
speaking on them or different members talking about what it is they do even if
you just
get one little tip or if it just makes you feel a bit more confident and it's
definitely
worth just just having them on in the background and even if it just gets you a
bit more motivated
because sometimes you can get a bit like getting a bit of a little can't we so
yeah have a
look at the training on our website and invest money in your webcam set up and
outfits yeah
so if you're treating this like you know like it's a job and and it's your
business you
know you're self-employed so you can invest a little bit of money from what you
're making
back into you know your setup of course and we always go on about lighting like
having
good lighting having a HD webcam is really important if you can and ring lights
and things
you can get really good ring lights for like 30 quid that makes such a huge
difference
and I know Georgia likes to have and I've got like little lights that you can
have in
the background it's nice to have a little lighting in the background and then
your big
light facing you behind the setup and of course any outfits so depending on
what your webcam
persona is just trying out different outfits and different things at different
time of
day like sometimes I'll come home from the gym and just come in my gym gear and
some
guys like that or sometimes pyjamas obviously lingerie like just testing out
different things
to see what works and because you're self-employed you can claim these back
when you do your expenses
so anything that you spend you know lingerie make up lighting all of that stuff
you can
claim that back and you don't have to be tapped on that stuff.
Set a schedule and say yeah this is something that's good especially if you're
in a rot
or you know if you just want to start treating it a bit more seriously and
making a bit more
money from it then setting a schedule can really help and I mean the beautiful
thing
about cameras that you can fit around your lifestyle but sometimes that means
that you
can get a bit I know I can get a bit like oh you know have had a long day maybe
I'll
just do tomorrow but if you're setting your schedule beforehand you know how
many hours
you want to do you're keeping to that and even on those quiet days you know you
're going
to be on you know you're going to be on for a certain amount of hours so it's
likely
that you'll make it back so setting schedule is really important and keeping
yourself
to it you know keeping yourself motivated and I think with that as well it's
always
worth like to keep yourself motivated and to keep to your schedule it's always
worth
looking at what you've earned over like a week or even a month rather than
every time
you go on because sometimes we all know that we can have a quiet day and then
you know
motivation can slip and it's like oh another long day it was quite yesterday
maybe I'll
leave it but actually if you look at your earnings over like a couple of weeks
or even
a month it's usually quite surprising isn't it what you've earned you know and
if I look
back I think I'll be quite quiet lately but then I'll look back at the month
and if you
haven't like hundreds and I'm like oh actually yeah okay let's just stick to my
schedule and
get back on and this is a big one and something that actually I don't think we
've talked about
enough this I think came up in conversation with me and G recently and I was
like yeah
we should we should maybe even do a call on it or you know talk about this a
bit more
like creating a good energy in your chat room you know for a lot of guys a lot
of clients
this is somewhere that they come when they've had a stressful day maybe they're
not quite
getting on with their why you know they don't feel appreciated or they can't
bring their
whole selves to anybody else in their life so creating a good energy you know
an accepting
compassionate fun flirty energy it just brings you so many more clients and it
feels so
good for you as well as them you know and so yeah creating a good energy on
your chat
room and the ways to do that are making sure that you're in the right headspace
where you're
going on cam maybe having a little routine that you do beforehand to get you
ready wearing
things that you feel good in not that you think they are like that you feel
good in because
if you feel great in a pair of I don't know care they're pyjamas and you know
your energy
is great and you're flirting and there's banter you're going to earn much more
than if you're
all in this fancy beautiful lingerie and you're just not feeling it and you
know your energy is
up so you know thinking about your energy and looking after yourself comes in
that as well
doesn't it and that goes to what I've just said so wearing what makes you feel
good whether that's
you know lots of makeup not much makeup jamas lingerie whatever it is that
makes you feel good
that's going to come across to your clients um activist name so this is
something that I talk
about a lot um you know our film we can get stuck in this place where we think
that a webcam model
is a certain person or we think we should be saying certain things and I've
seen it with a lot of
girls you know people come in and they're immediately trying to be sexy but you
know or
trying really hard to be liked by that person but actually if you can just
settle back into
yourself a little bit just open up and actually listen to what they're saying
so not don't come
with an assumption that they're going to want this or that just settle back
because sometimes
you can get much better idea of what they like by just giving them a space and
a bit of time
and asking some questions rather than going in all guns blazing trying to be
sexy because
what is sexy is different to every person and that might not even be what they
're here for they
might be here because they want to just talk to you about something or tell you
something so
honing in on what they act what they're actually saying to you reflecting it
back to them sometimes
so that they know that you're hearing them and it's so good for building
relationships
and it can make you feel good as well because then you're you're more involved
um being compassionate so of course that comes with it you know I'm sure that's
you know for for every few guys that are lovely there's also a guide that's not
so lovely
but what we don't want to do is just become fixed on that or bringing our views
about you know
men in general from the outside world into this space and it's just affecting
our energy on cam or
stopping us from being compassionate with our clients you know there are a lot
of people who
will come to us with stuff that we maybe don't want to hear and it's okay
completely okay to set
boundaries with what you will and won't talk about um but always coming with
the energy of
compassion until you figure out what those boundaries are you know um because
sometimes
you know you don't know if you're gonna you don't know if you're gonna gel with
someone
until you give them that open space and then actually you find out they're
really you know
they're really lovely and you can sort of build a relationship with them on cam
so
just being compassionate treating everybody with as an individual and knowing
that this is
their safe space to start with um it's great okay um so yes thank you
the different styles of webcam webcam can be whatever you make it and it's fun
to
explore the different styles of webcam to see what suits you once you found
what style or styles
you enjoy you can apply them to yourself you can then apply them and sorry I've
just I think I've
wrote that wrong there and so yeah when you found the right styles that fit you
you can apply
yourself to learn as much knowledge to learn as much as possible about this and
become an expert
remember knowledge is power so here are some examples of the different styles
of webcam
you can um you can do so there's gfe which is girlfriend experience and this
one is probably
quite I think it is yeah quite popular on webcam um and it's just more about
having like a gentle
chat and you know like a flirty chat and just giving them your time and
attention and kind of
like you would if you were chatting to your boyfriend um but yeah this is quite
a good one to maybe
start with if you know you're not really sure where to start because it's not
too hardcore and you
don't really need to know too much about you know a certain subject to be able
to do this one you
just have to actively listen and be compassionate and all the things that you
've just mentioned
earlier um just create a good space for them to come into your chat room and um
yeah that's
the girlfriend's experience we do actually have more training on all of these
different styles as
well and so yeah you can always look into each one a little bit more if you
need more guidance
and another style is the horny housewife so this one is also quite popular see
a lot of people
doing this one and you can always write on your profile you know my husband
works away and
I'm always in the house on my own and I'm bored and horny and you know want to
want to explore
like webcam and want to explore this with like you know with you guys and yeah
they love this one
I think this is one super popular and this is probably one that I'll start to
do as I get a little
bit older I'll probably try that one out and but yeah I think this is a good
one as well and another
style is to be a dominatrix or to be a submissive and so obviously they're both
on the other ends
of the spectrum and and once again we have so much training on both of these
subjects we actually
have a course on each one of them and both are as well very popular on cam and
one of them the
dominatrix is one that I've done like the whole time I've been on cam and well
you used to do the
submissive kind of stuff now but you've changed me to more switch haven't you
or doing a bit of both
and so yeah both of them are very popular so I definitely looking to learn a
more about even
off them or both of them if you're comfortable to explore this on webcam and
another persona you
can look into and try is a shy innocent type so the kinds like this one because
they feel like
they can like guide you on this journey and look after you and stuff like that
so it's always good
to play this one even if you're not shy in a sense you can still play on it and
to be honest even
though I do focus mainly on dominatrix even if there's a client that comes into
my room that
one skill friend experience or that wants to you know that I can tell that he
wants me to be a
little bit more vulnerable and shy and whatnot then I'll just I'll just do that
because unless
it goes out of my comfort zone I'll really do anything to make the money so if
it's just something
I just have to like act like I'm shy for like an hour or whatever else and that
's fine with me
and so yeah it's good exploring different parts like different personas so
maybe you can change
it up for different clients but with that being said don't feel like you have
to do anything that
you're uncomfortable with and another style is taboo so this is something that
you're a little
bit more experienced in right Sami and I'm not so experienced in this one to be
honest but
like I said you can always look into this a little bit more and yeah I think it
's quite popular on
calm would you say Sami I'm sure you do quite well with it and sorry my sound
was muted because
I've been putting up my makeup and stuff yeah it's really popular and if anyone
wants to know
anymore they can just message me and I'll give them some tips and bits and bobs
if they want to
know anything sorry is that fine perfect everyone knows what was that sorry I
said it's not for
everyone you need to be like you know it's not everyone's cup of tea but if it
is your cup of tea
then I've got lots of information for you if you want to message me or whatever
perfect thank you
and yeah with this one as well I think you just have to be careful of checking
adult works rules
because I know there are certain things that you definitely can't talk about on
calm or
you know you can't do or whatever else like taboo subjects so yeah just make
sure you know
exactly what you kind of can't do because you don't want to be getting you know
any warnings or
your profile maybe deleted or anything like that but yeah we can guide you in
the right direction
there if you need more help with that one and finally connection make your
client feel safe
so no matter what style of webcam you're doing it's the connection that's going
to keep your
clients coming back and keep them hooked and you know keep them spending for
years and years and
years if they feel a true genuine connection to you trust me they will not
leave you I have had
clients for the whole time I've been on webcam which is nine years I've still
got clients I've
been coming from the first year all the way up to now and that's because we've
got a connection
and we've been you know keeping it going for all this time so yeah like just
going back to what we
were saying earlier about just creating a good energy in your chatroom actively
listening make
your client feel safe so not like not judging them or making them feel you know
making them feel
like what they're saying is yeah like just no judgment I think just trying not
to like judge
them or make them feel judged and yeah just create a safe space and trust me
they will keep coming
back and but yeah I think this is like the main thing really on cam is like
really just to connect
with them because they're not here to just see like a beautiful woman they're
here to have a real
connection because if they did want to just see that they would just go watch
something online for
free the pain to have this conversation with you and have this connection and
finally what is your
unique selling point so have a little think about that about what you can offer
and you can write
about it in your profile or of course you know you'll show this or present this
to your clients
whatever it is and I used to have a poll in my house for example I still do but
not in this
house be like in in Australia and I never used to go in it on cam when I was in
Australia and I was
like why aren't I going on this again because when I used to do it years ago it
used to draw people
in and then say oh where's the poll today you're going to get back on the poll
today so so yeah
it's like that would be something that I could use as a unique selling point to
the fact that
I've got a poll there I can dance on the poll for them because not everyone
online is going to have
that and so yeah it could just be something as simple as that just certain
objects in your house
or whatever else but yeah have a little think about what yours could be and
definitely use it on cam
for sure okay so how to get more clients in your chat room so I'm sure most
people know this but
for any newbies so try bidding to be on the front page so it can really help so
I personally never
gone cam without bidding I always always will bid and basically what we can we
can show you this is
it's in the training it's in the um the beginners training how to do this and
your mental can show
you as well um but basically there's just a little box where you can put in a
certain amount of credits
to bid to be on the front page and you do it hour by hour so you need to do
this just a few minutes
before the hour George is really good at setting alarms on her phone if she's
going to be on cam
for a long time just like a five to the hour so that you can put your credits
in the little box
to bid to be on the front page for next hour um I sometimes keep myself because
I forget to do that
and then you're on an hour and you haven't been emphasized but yeah it really
really helps to be
on the front page it just stops the clients from having to click through and
through and through
load of pages of girls to find you and usually they're just going to click
through a couple of pages
and see who they like so yeah it helps to do that um you can also try free chat
so yeah just try it
you know different people feel different things about free chat because you're
obviously chatting
to people for free so you know you are you're doing a bit of labor for free but
hopefully you're
getting some of those people into your either group or private chat so you are
making some
money from it um and even if you just do it for five minutes when you go online
all for 10 minutes
you know just so that you'll pre-pause out there and you get seen and then you
can
hopefully reel people in from there um you can set the amount of time that
someone can be in your
free chat so that um it will kick them out after a certain amount of time just
so they're not
chatting to you for free indefinitely um so you can chat to your mentor about
uh where that box is
and how to do that um emailing old regulars when returning to cam at the time
are so it's so good
to keep regular if you can and like we've said to have a schedule for cam so
that you know you
you build up regulars because they know what kind of time and what kind of day
you're going to be on
um you know they like to be able to come and chat to the same person at the
same sort of time
around their day or work or whatever they've got going on um but of course
sometimes we go on
holiday or we just are really busy and we don't get on for a little while so it
can mean that you
then have to build up your clients again so it can be quiet unless you're
regularly on cam and
treating it like a business it can get quiet so one of the ways to um to make
yourself known
and to build yourself back up is to just go on your messages um and click
through your messages
and just reply to any messages or email your old clients um to let them know
that you're going to
be camming again um setting special offers so you can set special offers just
like gee was saying
you can make um like galleries for for clients and um you can also make special
offers for certain
clients or just in general you can do special offers to try and draw people in
um again you can
speak to your mentor if you're not sure how to do that um and make a social
media for your cam
persona to direct clients to your AdultWork so yeah lots and lots of people
use Twitter um
obviously depending on how discrete you want to be when you're doing this um if
you're confident
enough and happy enough to create social media you can use Instagram or Twitter
whatever um
and it can bring lots of clients in I know that lot of my regulars say that
they go on Twitter to
find people to come with so yeah it can be really good just make sure way to
treat it like a business
as well um and update your pictures or your info so yeah I think um we had a
little list of things
that you can do but it's somewhere um before you go on cam just to boost your
profile so these
are a few things but if you even if you update like a couple of lines put a new
line in your profile
or just change some words around it can boost you um up further so that people
see your profile
because the ones that have most recently been updated will come up first um
your pictures as
well just as many pictures as you can get on there as many different styles are
good they don't all
have to be super sexy pictures either you know they can be just ones that look
a bit more casual
because that again makes them feel like they're connecting with you a bit more
um and if you
are updating your pictures especially your three profile pictures just make
sure you're doing it
um within nine to five on one day's because um they have to be modified before
they'll come up
so if you change your profile picture at like six p.m it might not be modified
and it might not
so you might be coming and you've got no profile picture so just make sure you
do that between nine
and five um and also to give the consent for all your pictures so every time
you upload a new
picture you need to click on the consent button and give your consent for it
and as well otherwise
it won't show um Sammy over to you beautiful picture of you as well
can you hear me now yes yeah oh good um finally I'm gonna get back
my phone is loud texting me hi kai you okay I'm fine
good um yeah so just a few little things that I um I've been taking notes as
well and all the
other stuff that you girls have been saying um my my advice would be um
positioning so bidden
for the front page I think it's like super important when you first start you
don't have any like
regulars yet um that you do this or if you go online when you go on before your
broadcast you
can see how many other girls are online so sometimes I normally come like night
times and
if I go on by like nine ten o'clock there's normally like six to seven hundred
other girls
online sometimes over seven hundred so I think bidding to be you know as far up
the pages you can
it's like super important and I just think it works so well and yeah that would
be something that I
would always do as well now um unless I know I've got a regular come in then
you know it's a little
bit different if you're established and you've got regulars but I think if you
're going on at a
time that your record is not might not be on or you're new or whatever then
yeah a definitely
position because a couple of credits just means like nothing when you can earn
you know if you can
be in a private for like an hour or half an hour or even four five minutes you
know like them so
worth it um so keeping notes of returning clients to build up regular clients
okay so this is something
that I've always done or did at the start still do now if I have someone come
on that I haven't
spoken to before and then I see them come again I'd be like oh okay and I just
have it's my next
card next to me like I've been making notes tonight and I just write they use a
name a few notes about
what we've spoken about and um what to say next time or how to remember them or
whatever because
when they come back they always remember you so they always look like a high
beautiful um
power show weekend like maybe you've told them something and then you're like
oh shit I don't
I can't remember saying that who are you like do you know what I mean so if you
don't remember
then they're probably not going to come back but if you're like oh yeah it was
great thank you so much
like how was yours did you go to that festival on Saturday or did your wife
like that outfit that
you bought her or or anything you know like anything they tell you but it's
like key points
write it down I even write stuff like um remember to ask them how's their dog
like they got dog you
know like her or remember to ask them if their wife's okay they like to always
talk about their
wife you know like anything like that because it when they do come back and you
can you're like
her oh you can just like you can have a read it before you go online or you can
just like have it
next to you just glance at have a little flick through um they'll be like oh
wow she remembers me
I'm really special and I think that's so important to make clients feel special
because like we were
saying they want a connection and they want you to think that they're like your
favourite client or
like you've remembered them like that means so much and I think it goes like a
long long way
but it's massively worked for me so I just think that yeah that's something
that I would definitely
advise everyone to do um placement of subjective objects okay so if you are
offering this is something
that I used to always do and I forgot about it till recently um if you're
offering um put like
pussy play or arse play or any kind of play or sucking the dildo or whatever or
whipping or any
kind of toys or or sort of props have them like seductively placed behind you
or around you like
not like a oh wow there's some dildo maybe necessarily but like maybe like a
little one popping out
of my underneath a pillow or like one left on a shelf or do you know what I
mean like I think
and then they're like oh what's that and you're like oh that's my favourite toys
and it can get the
conversation going and then they can be like oh what do you like to do is that
or whatever and I think
like when blippers come in like we all have they just come in and leave again
if they see that they
might be a bit like whoo that's that and start conversation um yeah so I just
think that's a little
little tip that I would say um that that works also white bedding can be really
good when I first
started I thought what guys don't really care about that but if you you know if
you're new and
you just I just feel like you stand out more and there's mine depending on
persona
because I'm glad we're like darker like darker stuff and whatever and don't
stress too much about
it but sometimes I think oh if you've got like your tan on and you've got like
a bright outfit
or whatever you do stand out a little bit more against white bedding sort of
like neutral
nice tidy backgrounds and stuff like that um yeah lighting super important I
can have this new
little ring light that I've clipped to my laptop because I break my ring lights
all the time and
I've got quite pretty like fairy lights in the front of my room like in front
of me and I've got a
red soft light above me and then I have this that's on now that I just clicked
in front of me um
personally I think lighting changes a room whatever even if you're not coming I
think you
could have stuff as in you put lovely lighting in and it would look amazing so
yeah I think I'm
quite swappy um and visualization and manifestation so this is probably my top
tip to everyone
before I go on cam I take at least five minutes to just sit and have some
downtime like I have
a little mantra in my head think about how I want the next however long to go
so say I'm starting
at 10 and I only want to work till 12 so I'll be like I'm going to finish at 12
um I'm going to
I'm going to um I want um this person to come in this person to come in oh I
want to have this
conversation I've shot my eyes and I think no I'll like play the whole
conversation out in my head
I'll visualise what amount of money I want to earn like as if I can see it
already in my bank account
um yeah like say the same kind of things over and over and over to myself like
I've
liked some candles I'll be really calm getting the right mindset because I
think if you go on cam
and you're quumpy or you've had a bad day or you're stressed you're not going
to make any money you
might as well just have some time off and you know look after yourself and go
back on cam when you're
feeling better because again it's like that connection guys can tell a straight
away body
language what you know what energy you're giving off um but I basically live my
life manifest in it
and if I said this like two years ago or someone has said this to me two years
ago I would have been
like what I know I literally live in my dream life and it's I swear to you
girls it works every single
time um so I talk to like everyone a little bit more about this maybe on
Thursday so I'm going to
do a little meditation on Thursday for whoever I'd like to come um because
otherwise I'd just be
chatting to you all night about it and I don't want to think up loads of your
time so yeah but I just I
do really think that's so important just like that five minutes before you go
on to like really
go through in your mind and visualise it as if it's already happened as if you
've like finished
or shift before you start it thank you sir yeah so you're probably seeing my
boobs most of the time
then I think there's there was one more though sorry that um you skip past it
if you've seen it
but um remember you've said about checking the clients in your free chat to see
which ones have
credits oh yes sorry I have no glasses on sorry um so yes when your when
clients come uh into your
free chat they will have written next to their name if they've got it was like
credits they'll be
highlighted in purple I think and then guys who don't have credits they just
won't have anything
next to their name so always be aware of that when you're chatting with boys in
three
pay more attention to the guys with the purple highlighted credits next to
their name because
they've got money yeah thank you sammy that's okay okay um don't need to do
this one j
yeah sure this was your one wasn't it the one that you made and I'll do the
last one
okay so so looking after yourself is so important you know it goes alongside
everything we've said you know unless you're looking after yourself you can't
set schedules
you can't manifest you can't be in a good space you can't create a safe space
for other people
or you know you have to look after yourself before any of that so yeah it's
just important for us
to to acknowledge and to to drum that message home um some ways that you can do
that are to
make sure that you have boundaries that suit you so of course you know it you
're what you want
to do what you want to talk about all that stuff may change over time it may
not be completely rigid
but at least if you have an idea about what your hard limits are what you're
absolutely
not going to do then you know that you're not going to be swayed um to do
things that you're
not happy with um I think you know we always say for every you know client that
you feel a bit
uncomfortable with you know if you're spending time with them you're
potentially not making the
space to be with a client that you would really enjoy trying with so not
feeling that you really
have to you know continue a chat and be pushing yourself to to even doesn't ask
me doing anything
you don't want to do even just be you know having a conversation with someone
that doesn't have
the right energy that's making you feel a bit off you know if that happens you
're more than within
your rights just kick them out of your room or just to tell them you know you
're you're gonna chat
to somebody else now or whatever else you know it's your incomplete control so
just make sure that
you're aware of your boundaries and that you're aware of how you feel when you
're coming with
anybody and you don't need to find an excuse not to talk to anybody
it's completely fine just to just cut them off if you don't if you don't want
to tell them
um have fun like this is so important because this is the energy in your room
isn't it
whether or not you're having fun is the energy in your room you know like if
whether you want to
have some like music on or you're watching something in the background or you
know you're doing something
else you're just enjoying yourself and you're actually engaged in the chat and
you you're having fun
maybe having a bit of banter you know I always come with like a bit of a funny
story or something
you know I'll just make it up or just take inspiration from friends or TV or
whatever
and just something fun or funny that I can say to them and that just engages
them and it gets me
laughing and them laughing and just nice to have fun when you're on camera it's
a way to look after
yourself as well um checking in with yourself so you know it's all well and
good knowing what
your boundaries are but it's more important to check in with yourself you know
regularly to actually
check in how do I feel in this moment you know is this okay with me you know
how can which way
can I take this conversation or just to notice if you get like a sensation in
your body or maybe
you're a bit triggered by something just keep checking in with yourself you
know and that means I know
it can be hard when your attention is out on the client and you're thinking
about them but it's
really important to bring that attention inward sometimes just have a quick
check in am I okay
yeah great and then to carry on you know so checking checking in with yourself
is the only way that
you're going to know what your boundaries are because your body will tell you
body will tell you what's
what's good for you and what's not so listening to it is really important and
ask for support if
there's anything you're not sure about or even something like that you've
talked about that you
that's made you feel a bit weird or just you're not sure about your boundary or
something you know
just please ask in the group because there's so many supportive amazing women
in the group or
speak to your mentor or one of us and we'll be more than happy to talk to you
about it so you don't
ever feel like you're on your own um and prioritise your well-being so you know
looking after you is
important this is the reason why we do this we're doing this to like create a
better life for ourselves
and you know to earn money and to manifest and for all these amazing things
that we're going to do
to travel to whatever else so just keeping that in your mind that you know the
reason you're doing
this is for you so you don't want to eat you know you don't want to lose sight
of that you know
just prioritise your well-being so important and finally okay so we'll finish
on some extra
things to note so something that we've already said on this call and what it is
actually so important
and it's a keeper note of your regular clients and useful information your
clients want a relationship
with you so yeah I don't need to speak on that much more because we've already
covered that
but it is super super important again do our online training courses and watch
the training videos
and there's so many different things to take inspiration from on there and
you might learn about something a subject that you never thought that you'd be
interested in
or want to do on cam but then you might learn start watching the course and
learn about it and think
actually I think I'd be quite good at that so yeah just take a little look
through and see what
stands out to you and you can also ask the other members for advice in our
WhatsApp support groups
and you'll get a diverse range of answers and obviously everyone's cam style is
a little bit
different even if you are in the same nation doing the same sort of thing each
individual person will
have their own way of doing it so if you have anything that you need more
advice on you can always
ask in the WhatsApp chat and the girls are also lovely and they'll respond with
like really good
answers and so yeah that's something you can do as well don't ever feel shy to
ask for help in the
chat and don't be afraid to ask the client if you don't understand what they've
said so yeah don't
feel like you have to have it all figured out um some clients like we said
earlier like to guide
you along this journey and feel like they're helping you so asking them
questions some of the
clients will actually really love that of course some won't and that's okay you
know but um but
yeah if they ever say anything like an abbreviation or just if they mention
anything at all that
you're not quite sure on just ask just say oh what do you mean by that I'm not
quite sure what you
mean and then and then yet they'll just explain it to you so don't feel like
you have to try and
come up with the answer in your head and just ask the clients um update your
profile regularly to
be in the top of searches so we've already touched on that one and well yeah
this is quite important
as well treat this like a business set working hours and writing on your
profile so if you are
able to set a schedule then you can actually just write on your profile what
days and times
you're going to be online so you can just have in your bio um upcoming
availability over the next
week or when I'm next online and then just write Monday 24th 2 p.m. To 5 p.m.
Tuesday 25th 9 p.m. To
6 p.m. Well 9 p.m. To 6, 9 to whatever you know whatever it is just write in on
your profile and
then when your clients view your profile they'll say oh she's going to be
online on Tuesday night
perfect I can come in on Tuesday and then they'll come back to see you and so
yeah that's something
I would do if you can set a schedule and invest in yourself and your brand so
we mentioned this as
well earlier and I feel like this is like this is your business so like any
business you need to
invest time money energy into it and the more you invest into it the more you
're gonna get like
trust me like if you just put the if you put the time into it and you really
you really focus on
doing the best that you can out of this then yeah it will it'll definitely um I
've got an
own model that we've already done it will definitely like show you know what I
mean how well you're
doing um do your research read blogs and online content and so yeah do your
research by doing our
training or just research online you can read blogs and all these things are
going to help you
on cam especially with certain areas of webcam you have to know exactly what
you're talking about
with each thing so domination for example even just that one the subject alone
so many different
types of domination you can do so it's always good to just research and just
get as much knowledge as
possible about this subject that you're doing so then you can um yes then you
're not going to run
out of things to do or stay with your client and finally take inspiration from
over webcam
models so you can go online and see what gills are um see what gills are on the
front page and then
I would always look at the ones that have quite a lot of ratings click on to
them because then
usually they're more established and have better profiles and um yeah you can
take a look at what
they're writing on the profile what type of pictures to use what type of word
and they use
and um yeah take inspiration from them okay so bring us to the end
yeah does any questions yes any questions sorry or anything that they want to
add like
any little tips that that maybe we haven't covered um I was going to say
briefly
maybe it's good to be aware of things that you can't do on cam as well because
I know some people
get caught out with getting warnings from out of work so just to know a couple
of things up
top of my head you can't have your phone showing on cam so if you're on cam you
know just have your
phone beneath the screen so that they can't see it if you're going to be using
it because you
can get warning for that and not having other people in the background um
obviously you don't
have to unless it's a couples profile and you've got consent for that for the
other person to be
there there shouldn't be anybody else in the background or even if they're just
walking past
quickly you'll probably get a warning for that just be aware I don't know if
there's any other
yeah um no dogs or well not dogs no animals at all in the background like they
don't allow that
and um I think no photos of like anybody and knowing your pictures if you have
a photo of
you on your profile and there's a picture in the background like for example
that small one there
you can see in the corner even if it's just small like that they still don't
like it and um I think
that's also the same on cam so try not to let any photos be in the background
of other people
and maybe we could do a little list and put it on our put it on the um thing on
the website
like the members area we could have a little list of don't actually because
they do change
quite often as well don't they say it's quite hard to remember everything isn't
it so I think
even I would like to look back at that and be like oh yeah we've got about that
one do you know what
I mean um yeah it would be an idea yeah but I think they're the main ones that
we've just said
well come with people else but yeah there's probably a few more that we can add
in there
um but yeah no one walk and passes like that's the main one is no other people
get caught out for
is allowing other people on their cam um so yeah just don't do that one
and I was just saying yeah she's like that she got a warning on her profile if
you do get a warning
on your profile then speak to your mentor or one of us and we can look into it
for you so
we can ask them what the reason is and yeah we can contact them from our side
so yeah just let us
know if you've got any issues like that um I just wanted to if I could add as
well um I just was
text I just text Hannah and asked if it was okay because she can't speak
because she hasn't got any
working camera on her uh in the meeting and she just said that she sent me a
really lovely
message earlier saying that she spent like three hours last night going through
like the
site going through all the training really put some time into it completely re
wrote all of her profile
um featured but SMS today and did like some hardcore manifestation as she said
and she got
like she's literally got she's so busy at the moment she's private messaging
someone
and texting like a new slave already who's pissing himself in the bar like he
he's a long term now
client for her and that was just from one night of doing that little bit of
extra work and I'm just
I just think it's amazing and I just wanted to be like oh it does work you know
like if you do if you
can believe in it and put your mind to it and do the work it really can work
amazing for you so
yeah I just wanted to share that with you the bad kids so that's fine
yeah well done for that it's such a nice feeling isn't it when you put some
effort and time in and
it plays out the world and I was like I'm so happy I'm so happy that you've
done that I'm so happy
and yeah it's so much funny like it's funny like it's funny
I've just seen your message Danny that would be absolutely amazing thank you if
you could send
it to one of us because Danny has a list of what's not allowed so that would be
amazing thank you
we can add to the website
any other questions anybody or anything else sad
now
okay well I think that's us for today then that that was that went
it was quite nicely an hour wasn't it yeah so thank you so much to everyone for
coming
it's lovely to see some of you and we'll let you know soon when the next call
is going to be
thank you oh sorry sorry sorry on Thursday I'm just doing a little
a very quick like manifesting meditation I'll post in all of the groups if
anyone would like to
come it's just not like a not not a massive fool just a little 20 minutes sort
of little
witching manifestation oh thank you Sami that's amazing
and please if there's any other subjects or anything we've mentioned that you'd
like to see a bit
more training on please we'll always have to have feedback on what you'd like
um because we're
happy so Taylor it's a what you want so if that is no okay good luck to anyone
that's going on tonight
thank you I'm going on tonight too yeah have a good night every more day thank
you
bye bye